Contact

dina14398@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dina-mostafa-a995351b2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Consulting
Customer Experience
Interviewing

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
Arabic (Native or Bilingual)

Dina Mostafa

Human Resources Generalist at KnowledgeNet Qesm El Maadi

Summary

I am a very dedicated person who is looking to grow and build a professional career, I have Two years of experience in Human Resources Field with educational background, Moreover, I am eager to learn a new thing everyday and every minute. Providing life with passion and excitement for everything around.

Experience

KnowledgeNet Human Resources Generalist April 2022 - Present (2 months) Cairo, Egypt

- Recruits, interviews, and facilitates the hiring of qualified job applicants for open positions; collaborates with Technical managers to understand skills and competencies required for openings.
- Conducts or acquires background checks and employee eligibility verifications.
- Implements new hire orientation and employee recognition programs.
- Gather and analyze data with useful HR metrics, like time to hire and employee turnover rates.
- Reviews, tracks, and documents compliance with mandatory and non-mandatory training, continuing education, and work assessments. This may include safety training, anti-harassment training, professional licensure, and aptitude exams and certifications.
- Performing routine tasks required to administer and execute human resource programs including but not limited to compensation, benefits, and leave; disciplinary matters; disputes and investigations; performance and talent management; productivity, recognition, and morale; occupational health and safety; and training and development.
- Handles employment-related inquiries from applicants, employees, and supervisors, referring complex and/or sensitive matters to the appropriate staff.
- Attends and participates in employee disciplinary meetings, terminations, and investigations.

Maintains compliance with federal, state, and local employment laws and regulations, and recommended best practices; reviews policies and practices to maintain compliance.

- Performs other duties as assigned.

Alnafitha IT

Technical Talent Acquisition Specialist June 2021 - March 2022 (10 months)

- Partnering with key stakeholders and technical managers to build a best-inclass recruiting process.
- Design job descriptions and interview questions that reflect each position's requirements.
- Handle company recruitment process (Screen, filter & conduct Phone screening and face-to-face interviews).
- Work closely with marketing department to develop creative ways for addressing talent acquisition challenges.
- Managing hiring processes via electronic Applicant Tracking Systems.
- Attend career and college fairs, and similar events Handle candidates onboarding process.
- Support in Employee Performance Management & Employee Relationship Management.
- Support in Training & Development Programs
- Build Database and pipeline of qualified candidates according to hiring Needs.
- Report and analyse our Database to reach optimum efficiency.
- Responsible for preparing Job descriptions for new positions.
 Handle the resignation of existing employees and on-time replacement.
- Provide regular reports to the top management and provide decision makers

with the proper information to take the right decision regarding company

- human capital.
- Conduct exit interviews on resigning erminating employees
- Support in other HR functions when needed
- Perform other tasks as assigned.

Heart to Heart Consulting & Human Development. Human Resources Specialist June 2020 - May 2021 (1 year)

- Responsible for the Talent acquisition and Performing in-person and phone interviews with candidates.

- Identify training needs and create or procure professional development curriculum.
- Monitor training programs to ensure that training objectives are met.
- Provide input on workforce and succession planning as well as plans business unit restructuring.
- Find ways to build morale, improve workplace relationships, and boost productivity and retention.
- develop policies, programs, and solutions.
- Interpret human resources policy to company management.
- Consult regularly with management and provide guidance when appropriate.
- Develop talent acquisition strategies and hiring plans.
- Perform sourcing to fill open positions and anticipate future needs.

VOIS

1 year 6 months

Technical Customer Support July 2019 - May 2020 (11 months)

- -Delivered customer service for the Technical queries for Vodafone AU and UK customers.
- provided timely and effective resolution to a wide range of customer queries related to contracts.
- built customer satisfaction, loyalty, to ensure meeting high volume of KPI standards.
- Act as high level of technical escalation within Customer Operations and support the internal operational entities toward problem resolution.
- Created and Reviewed any internal root cause analysis (RCA) applicable to their customers and generated customer-faced RCA to be communicated to customers.

International Account Advisor December 2018 - June 2019 (7 months)

- Kept records of customer interactions and transactions, recording details of inquiries, complaints, and comments, as well as actions taken.
- Resolved customers service or billing complaints by performing activities such as exchanging merchandise, refunding money, and adjusting bills.
- Checked to ensure that appropriate changes were made to resolve customers problems.
- Contacted customers in order to respond to inquiries or to notify them of claim investigation results and any planned adjustments.

- Referred unresolved customer grievances to designated departments for further investigation.
- Determined charges for services requested, collect deposits or payments, and/or arrange for billing.

Dublish

Translator

September 2018 - November 2018 (3 months)

- Read given material and research industry-specific terminology.
- Convert text and audio recordings from one language to one or more others.
- Ensure translated content conveys original meaning and tone.
- Prepare subtitles for videos and online presentations.
- Proofread translated texts for grammar, spelling and punctuation accuracy.
- Edit content with an eye toward maintaining its original format (e.g. font and structure).
- read through original material and rewrite it in the target language, ensuring that the meaning of the source text is retained.
- use specialist dictionaries, thesauruses and reference books to find the closest equivalents for terminology and words used.
- consult with experts in specialist areas.
- proofread and edit final translated versions.

Education

The American University in Cairo Human Capital Proffesional Diploma

The American University in Cairo HR Analytics Certificate

El Institute Cervantes El Cairo Spanish Language and Literature

Faculty of languages and translation at Misr university for science and Technology

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Language Interpretation and Translation · (2015 - 2019)